Guide to the Eugene B. Dynkin papers, 1950-2014.
Dynkin, Eugene B. papers,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Eugene B. Dynkin papers, 1950-2014.
14-19-4151
E. B. (Evgeniĭ Borisovich), Dynkin, 1924-2014.
36 cubic feet.
Correspondence, photographs,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Papers documenting the work, writings, and teachings of Dynkin. Collection includes digitized copies of audio and video interviews with mathematicians conducted by Eugene Dynkin, as well as biographical information and photos of these prominent mathematicians.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Professor at Cornell University from 1977-2014. Lie groups were the main subject of Dynkin's earlier research. "Dynkin's Diagrams" are widely used by mathematicians and physicists. After 1954, probability theory became the central field of his interests. Principal efforts were devoted to Markov processes and their connections with potential theory and partial differential equations.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Papers documenting the work, writings, and teachings of Dynkin. Collection includes digitized copies of audio and video interviews with mathematicians conducted by Eugene Dynkin, as well as biographical information and photos of these prominent mathematicians.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Dynkin, E. B. (Evgeniĭ Borisovich), (Evgeniĭ Borisovich), 1924-2014.
Subjects:
Mathematics.; Mathematics -- Study and teaching.; Mathematics -- History. -- Soviet Union
INFORMATION FOR USERS
NOTES
See also: Eugene B. Dynkin Collection of Mathematics Interviews digital collection, which consists of digitized interviews from this collection. http://dynkincollection.library.cornell.edu
SERIES LIST
Series I. Author Files
Series II. Publications by Eugene B. Dynkin
Series III. Research Material and Notes
Series IV. Talks and Conferences
Series V. Course Material
Series VI. The Situation in Soviet Mathematics
Series VII. General Documents
Series VIII. Personal and Biographical Material
Series IX. Audio/Visual material
Series X. Digital files
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Author Files
  - Subseries Ia. Alphabetical Files, group 1
    - Adelson-Velsky, Georgy, 1949, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Adler, Robert J., 1989-1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Agranovich, M.C., Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Agrawala, Vishnu, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Airault, Helene, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Akiyama, Hiroshi, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Aldous, David, 1983-1997 (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
    - Andre, Clement, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Aumann, Robert J., 1956-1981 (Box 1, Folder 10-11)
    - Azema, Jacques, 1972-1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Azencott, Robert, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Ballmann, Werner, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Bass, Richard F., Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Bauer, Heinz, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Berest, Yuri, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Biane, Philippe, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Billingsley, Patrick, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Bismut, Jean Michel, 1977-1981 (Box 1, Folder 20-21)
    - Blackwell, David, 1953-1977 (Box 1, Folder 22-23)
    - Blumenthal, Robert, 1957-1985 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Borel, Armand, 1952-1961 (Box 1, Folder 25-26)
    - Bott, Raoul, 1951-1958 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Boukricha, Abderrahman, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Brandolini, L., Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Brelot, Marcel, 1955-1988 (Box 2, Folder 3-6)
    - Brouck, William, 1971-1977 (Box 2, Folder 7-8)
    - Browder, W., 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Account of a train ride in Russia
    - Brydges, David, 1982-1989 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Burkholder, D.L., 1972-1989 (Box 2, Folder 11-12)
    - Cameron, R.H., 1944-1954 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Carmona, Rene, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Cartier, P., 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Cattani, Eduardo, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Caubet, Jean-Pierre, 1965-1978 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Chacon, R.V., Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Chavel, Isaac, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Chen, Zhen-Qing, 1990-1996 (Box 2, Folder 20-21)
    - Chentsov, Nikolai, 1956-1990 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Choquet, Gustave, 1958-1962 (Box 2, Folder 23-24)
    - Cox, Ted, 1977-1988 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Cramer, Harald, 1959-1978 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Cranston, Michael, 1983-1998 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Cutler, Colleen, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Debreu, Gerard, 1962-1975 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Dellacherie, C., 1973-1977 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Delzant, Antoinez, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Deuschel, Jean-Dominique, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Dewitt-Morette, Cecile, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Diaconis, Persi, 1981-1987 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Dobrushin, R.L., 1978-1988 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Dokuchaev, 1986-1991 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Doleans, Catherine, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Doppel, Karl, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Dorogovtsev, A.A., 1994-2003 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Driver, Bruce, 1985-2006 (Box 3, Folder 14-17)
    - Dubins, Lester, 1965-1988 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Durrett, Richard, 1976-1999 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Eagleson, G.L., 1971-1975 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Eckmann, Beno, 1955-1981 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Elliott, Joanne, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Elliott, Robert, 1977-1986 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Elworthy, K.D., 1979-1985 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Emery, M., Undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Essen, Matts R., 1997 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Ershov, M.P., 1974-1979 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Esseen, Carl-Gustav, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Evans, Lawrence, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Evans, Steven, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Falkner,Neil, 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Farrell, R. H., 1962 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Feldman, Jacob, 1958-1971 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Fernique, X., 1966-1992 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Filippov, Aleksei Fedorovich, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Fischer, Pal, 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Fleming, Wendell, 1971-1979 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Fortet, R., 1949-1953 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Fraenkel, A., 1930 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Freidlin, M., 1980-1986 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Includes correspondence
    - Freiman, Grigori, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Freedman, David A., 1962-1979 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Frenkel, I.B., 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Freudenthal, Hans, 1953-1968 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Frid, 1969-1974 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Friedman, Avner, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Fristedt, Bert, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Frohlich, J., 1976-1983 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Gale, David, 1955-1974 (Box 4, Folder 10-11)
    - Gallavotti, G, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Gixman, 1950-1975 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Gindikin, Simon, Undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Glover, Joseph, 1981-1991 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Gnedenko, Boris, 1937-1959 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Golubitsky, Martin, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Gordina, Maria, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Gorostiza, Luis, 1988-1992 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Grayehb, M.N, 1954-1958 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Gray, Lawrence, 1976-1978 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Grenander, Ulf, 1952-1998 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Grigelionis, Bronius, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Grigor'yan, Alexander, Undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Groh, Jurgen, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Guivarc'h Yves, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Gyongy, Istvan, Undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Hajek, Jaroslav, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Hall, W.J., 1964 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Harish-Chandra, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Harlamov, Boris, 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Harper, L.H., 1964-1966 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Hartmann, Mark, 1986-1988 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Hawkes, John, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Heble, M.P., 1961-1963 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Hewitt, Edwin, 1953-1978 (Box 5, Folder 4-6)
    - Hille, Einar, 1951-1970 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Hinchin, A. Ya., 1952 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Holley, R., Undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Ibragimov, I.A., 1967-1972 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Ilbin, A.M., 1960-1963 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Ilyashenko, Yulij, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Jaffe, Arthur, 1973-1989 (Box 5, Folder 13-14)
    - Joffe, Anatole, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Jurek, Zbigniew, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Kac, Victor. G., 1969-1989 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Kaimanovich, Vadim, 1983-1993 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Kallianpur, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Kanda, Mamoru, 1978-1983 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Karatzas, Ioannis, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Karlin, Samuel, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Karpelevich, Undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Katok, A., 1967-1978 (Box 5, Folder 24-25)
    - Katsenelinboigen, Aron, Undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Kazhdan, 1967-1985 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Kellogg, R.B., 1977 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Kemeny, John G., 1961-1967 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Kendall, David G., 1953-1979 (Box 5, Folder 30-31)
    - Kendall, David G., 1965-1986 (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
    - Kendall, Wilfrid, 1985-1995 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Kesten, Harry, 1958-1977 (Box 6, Folder 4-9)
    - Kiefer, Jack, 1972-1980 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Kifer, Yuri, 1977-2000 (Box 6, Folder 11-12)
    - Kingman, John, 1963-1979 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Kinney, J.R., 1953 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Korolyuk, Valdimir, 1951-1962 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Koszul, Jean-Louis, 1950-1955 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Krӓmer, Manfred, Undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Krein, Mark Grigorievich, 1947-1964 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Krone, Stephen, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Knsch, H., 1979 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Kurdjumov, G.L, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Labutin, Denis, 1999-2005 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Lamperti, John, 1957-1962 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Landis, 1988-1998 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Lax, Peter, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - LeCam, Lucien, 1957-1995 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Lee, Tzong-Yow, 1989-1993 (Box 7, Folder 4-5)
    - Lehman, Erich L., 1962-1977 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Lewis, J.T., 1977 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Liang, Zhishum, 1981-1994 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Liao, Ming, 1992-2002 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Liggett, T.M., 1971-1981 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Linnik, Y.V., 1949-1972 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Livshits, A.N., 1992 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Lbus, Jrg-Uwe, 1990-1993 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Lwner, Karl (Loewner, Charles), 1938-1959 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Los, Jerzy, 1970-1987 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Lyons, Russell, 1990-1994 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Lyons, Terry, 1979-1992 (Box 7, Folder 17-18)
    - Maisonneuve, B., 1969-1989 (Box 7, Folder 19-20)
    - Malioutov, Mikhail, 1982-2005 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Malcev, Mikhail, 1943-1952 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Malyshev, V.A., 1981-1988 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - March, Peter, 1983-1993 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Marcus, Michael, 1988-1991 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Margulis, Gregory, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Martin-Lf, Anders, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Maruyama, Gisiro, 1955-1977 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Maruyama, Takeo, 1971-1986 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Maslov, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Mazziotto, G., 1986-1988 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Merzbach, Ely, Undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Metivier, M., 1972-1987 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Millar, P. Warwick, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Milman, D., 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Ming, Liao, 2001-2003 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Munemi, Miyamoto, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Mokobodzki, Gabriel, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Molčan, G.M., 1971-1975 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Morse, Marston, 1953-1965 (Box 8, Folder 7-8)
    - Moser, Jrgen, 1956-1958 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Mostow, George Daniel, 1949-1957 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Movshovich, 1969-1976 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Mucci, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Leonid, Mytnik, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Nagasawa, Maseo, 1959-1987 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Naimark, M.A., 1952-1965 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Nakao, Shintaro, 1972-1976 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Natanzon, S.N., 1979-1990 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Neretin, Yu. A., 1992-1996 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Newman, Charles, 1980-1984 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Neyman, Jerzy, 1962-1976 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Nguyen, Xuan-Loc, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Nirenberg, L., 1967 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Nisievich, L., 1953 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Ogura, Yukio, 1970-1982 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Okabe, Yasunori, 1973-1976 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Olejnik, O.A., 1949-1989 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Onoyama, Takuji, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Orey, Steven, 1973-1978 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Ornstein, Donald, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Ouvrard, Jean-Yves, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Panyushev, D.I., 1999 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Papanicolaou, G., 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Phillips, R.S., 1951-1977 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Pinksy, Mark, 1968-1994 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Pitman, Jim, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Pittenger, A.O., 1969-1973 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Polterovich, V.M., 1973-1976 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Pontraygin, Lev, 1939-1944 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Prohorov, Yuri, 1954-1960 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Radner, Roy, 1977-1988 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Rao, B.V. and M., 1968-1985 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Rao, C.R., 1955 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Ratner, Undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Rockafellar, R. Tyrrell, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Rckner, Michael, 1983-1992 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Rogers, L.C.G., 1980 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Rosen, Jay, 1983-2001 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Rosenblatt, M., 1959-1963 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Rosenfeld, B.A., 1991 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Rosenthal, L., 1963-1969 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Rozovskii, Boris, 1975-1996 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Rothaus, O.S., 1966-1978 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Rothschild, Bruce, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Samuels, Stephen M., 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Samelson, Hans, 1951-1956 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Samuelson, Paul, 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Sato, Ken-iti, 1976-1981 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Setti, A.G., Undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Sevastyanov, B.A., 1948-1968 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Sharpe, Michael, 1979-1989 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Shepp, L.A., 1962 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Shelov, G.E., 1951-1953 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Shparo, D., 1966-1968 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Shreve, Steven, 1983-1985 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Shwarz, A.S., 1953-1955 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Siebenthal, Jean De, 1949-1956 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Silverstein, M.L., 1969 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Singer, I.M, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Sirao, Tunekiti, 1953-1970 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Smale, Steve, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Snell, J.L., 1952-1980 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Steffens, J., 1989 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Sturm, Karl-Theodor, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Sudakov, V.N., 1969 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Sugita, Hiroshi, 1985-1988 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Sugiura, Mitsuo, 1959-1966 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Symanzik, K., Undated (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Sznitman, Alain-Sol, 1984-1996 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Taqqu, Murad, 1977-1987 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Taylor, J.C., 1972-1981 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Taylor, S.J., 1954-1981 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Toom, Andrei, 1968-1993 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Trakhtenbrot, B.A., 1984 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Tsetlin, Michael Lvovitch, 1961-1964 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Vavilov, Nikolai, 1995-1998 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Varadarajan, V.S., 1961-1963 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Vasiliev, N.B., 1969-1973 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Vilenkin, Naum Ya., 1947-1960 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Vishik, M., 1952-1961 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Watanabe, Takesi, 1958-1968 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Weiss, B., 1967-1975 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Weisfeiler, B., Undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Williams, R.J., 1985 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Yaglom, A.M., 1953-1989 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Yamato, Yuiti, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Yang, Wei-Shih, 1988-1993 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Yen, Chih Ta, 1958-1959 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Yosida, Kosaku, 1943-1983 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Yushkevich, A., 1965-1991 (Box 10, Folder 11-12)
    - Zakai, Moshe, Undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Zolotarev, Vladimir, 1958-1990 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Subseries Ib. Alphabetical Files, group 2
    - Arnold, V., 1998-2002 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Barlow, M.T., 1978-1990 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Baras, Pierre, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Berezin, F.A., 1957-1975 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Brezis, Ham, 1983-1997 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Burdzy, Krzysztof, 1988-1995 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Cartan, Henri, 1950-1955 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Chao, J.A., 1986 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Chung, K.L., 1951-1984 (Box 13, Folder 3-4)
    - Coxeter, 1984-2004 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Dawson, Donald, 1964-2009 (Box 13, Folder 6-10)
    - Delmas, Jean-Francois, 1996-2002 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Dindoš, Martin, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Dobrushin, R.L., 1952-1990 (Box 13, Folder 13-15)
    - Dobrushin, G.B., 1991-2010 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      Includes correspondence and last will and testament.
    - Doob, J.L., 1940-1973 (Box 13, Folder 17-18)
    - Doob, J.L., 1940-1973 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Doeblin, Wolfgang, 1937-1939 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Evans, Steven, 1985-2001 (Box 14, Folder 3-5)
    - Evstigneev, Igor V., 1969-2004 (Box 14, Folder 6-8)
    - Feller, William, 1946-1959 (Box 14, Folder 9-10)
    - Fitzsimmons, P.J, 1985-2012 (Box 14, Folder 11-12)
    - Fleischmann, Klaus, 1984-1997 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Fllmer, Hans, 1976-2008 (Box 14, Folder 14-15)
    - Freidlin, Mark, 1961-1998 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Fukushima, Masatoshi, 1964-1994 (Box 15, Folder 2-3)
    - Furstenberg, Harry, 1963-1971 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Gelfand, I.M., 1938-1961 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Gershman, Anatole, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Getoor, R.K., 1952-1998 (Box 15, Folder 7-10)
    - Girsanov, Igor, 1958-1967 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Golovina, 1945-1985 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Gross, Leonard, 1967-1991 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Gusein-Zade, Sabir, 1966-1988 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Hsu, Elton Pei, 1984-1994 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Hunt, G.A., 1954-1958 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Ikeda, Noboyuki, 1964-1992 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Iscoe, I., 1985-1993 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Ising, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Ito, Kiyosi, 1944-1976 (Box 16, Folder 3-6)
    - Jirina, Miloslav, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Kac, Mark, 1955-1978 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Kac, Victor G., 1968-2001 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Kakatuni, Shizuo, 1937-1975 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Karpelevich, F.I., 1951-2002 (Box 16, Folder 11-12)
      Includes papers in honor of and about Karpelevich.
    - Khasminskii, Rafail, 1958-2003 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Kirillov, Alexandre, 1957-1960 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Kolmogorov, Andre, 1928-1954 (Box 16, Folder 15-16)
    - Knight, F.B., 1962-1973 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Kostani, Bertram, 1958-1959 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Kronrod, A.S., 1939-1986 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Krylov, N.V., 1964-1991 (Box 17, Folder 3-5)
    - Kunita, Hiroshi, 1967-1984 (Box 17, Folder 6-7)
    - Kusuoka, Shigeo, 1979-1984 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Kuznetsov, S.E., 1970-2000 (Box 17, Folder 9-10)
    - Labutin, Denis A., 2001-2009 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Lamperti, John, 1962-1972 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Lawler, Gregory F., 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Le Gall, Jean-Francois, 1984-2008 (Box 17, Folder 14-17)
    - Le Gall, Jean-Francois, 1984-2010 (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
    - Le Jan, Y., 1987-1993 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Levin, Leonid, 1978-1981 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Lions, J.L., 1972 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Levy, M. Paul, 1952-1969 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - L I E Groups, 1975-2007 (Box 18, Folder 7-8)
    - McGovern, Collingwood, Undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - McKean, Henry P., 1955-1976 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Malliavin, Paul, 1975-1996 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Mandelbaum, Avishai, 1966-1992 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - March, Peter, 1985-1993 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Marcus, Moshe, 1990-2010 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Maz'ya, V.G., 1972 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Meyer, P.A., 1961-2004 (Box 19, Folder 1-6)
    - Meyers, Norman G., 1972-1974 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Minchenko, Andrey, 2007-2011 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Molchanov, Stanislav, 1966-1993 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Morozov, V., 1938-1942 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Motoo, Minoru, 1962-1989 (Box 19, Folder 11-12)
    - Mselati, Benoit, 2000-2003 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Nagasawa, Maseo, 1964-1977 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Ne'eman, Yuval, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Nelson, Edward, 1958-1973 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Neveu, Jacques, 1969-1992 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Nirenberg, Louis, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Norris, James R., Undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Olshanetsky, M.A., 1993 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Onishchik, A.L., 1956-2003 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Oshima, Yoichi, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Overbeck, L., 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Parthasarathy, K.R., 1977-1984 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - P.D.E., 1963-1994 (Box 20, Folder 2-3)
    - Lu=Ψ(u), 1990-1999 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - u+Lu=Ψ(u), 1937-1998 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Peres, Yuval, 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Perkins, Edwin, 1982-2004 (Box 20, Folder 7-12)
    - Petrovsky, I.G., 1938-1939 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Protter, Philip E., 1977-1989 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Piatietzky-Schapiro, 1957-1974 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Rao, B.V., Undated (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Ray, Daniel, 1954-1956 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Ren, Yanxia, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Revus, Daniel, 1966-1970 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Roelly, Sylvie, 1986-1993 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Rohklin, V.A., 1947-1989 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Rost, H., 1971-1983 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Rota, Gian-Carlo, 1962-1984 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Rosenknop, 1950-1991 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Saloff-Coste, L., 1998 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Salisbury, Thomas S., 1984-2000 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Salminen, Paavo, 1990-1994 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Sheu, Yuan-Chung, 1991-1996 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Schied, Alexander, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Shiga, Tokuzo, 1982-1988 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Schoen, Richard, Undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Schwartz, Loren, 1977-1981 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Serre, Jean-Pierre, 1953-1955 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Seregin, L.V., 1961-1963 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Sheppard, Patrick, 1981-1984 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Shiryaev, Albert, 1961-1984 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Shnirelman, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Shnol, E. E., 1953-2001 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Schur, I., 1959-1988 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Sinai, Ya., 1957-2001 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Skorokhod, Anatoly V., 1954-1994 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - SPDE, 1987-1990 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Spitzer, Frank, 1958-1974 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Stone, Charles, 1966-1971 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Stratanovich, 1959-1960 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Strichartz, Robert S., 1967-1983 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Stroock, Daniel, 1971-2008 (Box 21, Folder 23-24)
    - Taksar, Michael, 1968-1996 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Tanaka, Hiroshi, 1957-1997 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Tepylaev, A.V., 1991-1997 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Tits, Jacques, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Tsirelson, 1975-1987 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Tutubalin, 1961-1969 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Ueno, Tadashi, 1960-1992 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Uspensky, 1955-1993 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Vanderbei, R.J., 1980-2004 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Varadhan, S., 1967-1982 (Box 22, Folder 9-11)
    - Veron, Laurent, 1980-2008 (Box 22, Folder 12-16)
    - Veršik, A.M., 1968-1986 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Verzani, John, Undated (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Vinberg, Ernest, 1962-1999 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Volkonsky, Victor A., 1958-1970 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Vvedenskaya, N.D., 1953-1986 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Walsh, John, 1967-1977 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Watanabe, S., 1965-1970 (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
    - Wentzell, Alexander, 1959-1992 (Box 23, Folder 3)